Preliminary Guide to the Marvin Center Administrative Office records, 1948-2004 RG0052
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Student org activities, applications, and building use, 1968-2013, RG0052 Series 3
  - GW Chapel -1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - MCGB Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ACU-I Nomination Forms, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Marvin Center Space Charge Policy (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Recycling, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Signage - 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Colonnade Gallery, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Club Registration Policy discussion Group July 19, 88, 1988-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - GB Communications Committee Minutes-Sept. 23, 1985, 1985-09-23 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Handicap Lights-Space Planning (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - MCGB Minutes -1987, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - GB Budget '83-'84, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Procedures Committee C. 1980's (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Misc. Office Allocations, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Office Allocation Proc. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1982 Office Allocations, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1983 Campus Act. Office Prop (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Marvin Center Documentation for the 1896-1987 Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 2001-02 Office Agreements, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 2002-2003 Space Agreements (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Letter of Agreements, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Application for Student Organization Space, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Application for Student Organization Space, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Signed - Agreement for use of Student Office Space, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Application for Office Space in the Marvin Center, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Agreement for use of student office space, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Application for use of student space, 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Agreement for use of student office space, 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - MCGB Office Resources, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Admin, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Letter to JLP, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Letters to MC, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Office Enhancements, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - JEC Review, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Campus Radio, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Appointee Position, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Residence Hall Lottery Study Final Report, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Student Association, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - SASS Reorganization 1997, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - SASS Strategic Planning 1997, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Gail Short Hanson, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1993-1994, Kim Andle Chair (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Gail Short Hanson 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Marvin Center Posting Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - MCGB Minutes, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Office Access, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SORC Final Proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - MC Employee Manual (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1997-1998 Office space application (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - One Card, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Marvin Center Smoking Policy, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - SA Court Cases, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Letters to MCGB (meet annouc), 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 96-97 Program Board, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - GW Votes Initiative, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Building Use Service 93/94, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Office Space 1993-94, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1993 Student Association Yearbook, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Unsigned (blank) Agreement for use of Student Office Space (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Agreement for use of Student Office Space (completed), 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - MC 4th floor renovation, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 2012-2013 Summer and Academic Year Housing Agreement (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Communications committee reports (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Forms/Info services, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Budget Meeting Homecoming 12/6/91, 1991-12-06 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Spring '92 Schedules, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Scheduling Confirmations, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Schedule Forms (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Calendars Blank, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Bldg Use '91 '92, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Student Org Network (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Public Event Board (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Incoming Memos, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Applications for Appt., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Kim and Kamal's Notes for meeting, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Graduate Lounge, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - MC Mid-Term Late Study Report, 1990-03-07 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Outgoing Memos, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Centerpiece '91, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Space Allocations, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Kim's Notes 89/90, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Space Allocations, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Communications Committee, History of MCGB Fall '90-Spr '91, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Building Brochures (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ACU-I Info (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Jo's Motivation Workshop, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - MC Needs Survey (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - New Student Register 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The New Student Register 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - The New Student Register 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Constitution Revisions 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Constitution Revision 02-03, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Constitution Revisions 01-02, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Const. Review, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Constitutional and Bylaw Research (2/97), 1997-02 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Constitution, 1982-1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Constitutional Amendments 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Constitutions, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Procedures Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - MCGB-Constitution(s) Building Use Policy Office Space allocation comparative income (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - copy of the GB constitution (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - GW Tax exempt status, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Trial and Error, 1968-1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Hatchet Articles about Marvin Center (microfilm copies), 1973-1997 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Marvin Center History Info (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Senate Meeting Materials (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Sen. Staff Seat Reservation Forms (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Legislation Tracking (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Senate Room Setup (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Senate Elect Info (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - EVP Transition (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Senate Meeting #6, 2005-04-12 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Senate Meeting #10, 2005-02-08 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Senate Meeting #11, 2005-03-22 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Senate Meeting #13, 2005-04-19 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Mark '95-'96, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Senate Training Materials (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - EVP Goals - Lasky (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Senate Mtg #1 09/14/04, 2004-09-14 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 2004 Summer Expenditures (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Senate Mtg. #2, 2004-09-28 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Senate Mtg (Special Meeting) 10/05/04, 2004-10-05 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Special Meeting #2 and Regular Meeting #3 10/12/04, 2004-10 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Senate #4, 2004-10-26 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Senate Meeting #5, 2004-11-09 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Senate Meeting #6, 2204-11-16 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Senate Meeting #7, 2004-12-07 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Senate Meeting #8, 2005-01-18 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Senate Meeting #3, 2005-02-01 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Senate Meeting #12, 2005-04-05 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Student Org Registration binder (Box 8, Folder 49)